Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Architectural Drawings
  - Job No. 796-798
    - Langley Field Aeronautical Experimental Station, Job Nos. 796 & 796-A, B, D, E, F, G, I, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, S, T, W, X, Y, Z, AB, AE, AF, AM, AO, AR, AS, AT, AU, AV, AW, AX, BC & BJ, Hampton, Virginia, 1917-1918
      - Power House by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-D)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 3/2/1918; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 29-1/2x46-1/2 inches
            - Roof Plan and Bunker and Mezzanine Floor Plan (3), revised 7/23/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Typical Exterior Details and Exterior Wall Details of Coal Bunker (5) (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Cross Section on Line "A-A" (6) (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Longitudinal Section on Line "B-B" (7) (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Details of Stairs and Toilet Rooms (8), revised 11/6/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
          - Structural Drawings, 3/4/1918; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 29-1/2x46-1/2 inches
            - Footing Plan and Schedule (1-S), revised 7/25/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Concrete Plan of First Floor and Mezzanine and Miscellaneous Details (2-S), revised 8/15/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Plan of Bunker and Sections "A-A" through "D-D" (3-S), revised 5/14/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - First Floor Framing Plan and Detail of Typical Connection for Columns Supporting Bunker (4-S), revised 7/25/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Roof Framing Plan and Details of Trusses and Girders (5-S), revised 5/14/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
            - Detail of Bunker Truss "H" and Framing Plan at Southeast Corner of Bunker (6-S), revised 5/14/1918 (Map-case 26, Folder 11)
      - Airplane Hangar Unit by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-E)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, except as noted, 9/17/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 23-1/4x51-3/4 inches, except as noted
            - Plot Plan, Foundation Plan and Details of Columns (1), 8/13/1917; revised 11/2/1917 (Tube 59)
            - Floor Plan (2), revised 11/22/1917 (Tube 59)
            - Roof Plan, Roof Framing Plan and Detail of Lower Chord Bracing (3) (Tube 59)
            - Front, Rear and End Elevations and Transverse Section (4) (Tube 59)
            - Transverse Section and Truss and Other Details (5) (Tube 59)
            - End Elevation and Elevations of End of Rear, End of Front, Typical Windows and Typical Doorways (6), revised 11/22/1917 (Tube 59)
            - Revised Roof Plan and Details (7), 1/9/1918; 23-1/2x34-1/4 inches (Tube 59)
            - Details of Supports for Heaters in Hangars No. 1 & 2 (8), 8/27/1918; 17-1/2x30-1/4 inches (Tube 59)
          - Structural Drawing, 11/24/1917; pencil-on-vellum drawing, 16-3/4x21-1/2 inches
            - Details of Plates for Support Curtain (1-S) (Tube 59)
          - Mechanical/Electrical Drawing, 11/1/1917; ink-on-linen drawing, 23-1/4x51-3/4 inches
            - Plan and Section Showing Wiring and Details of Water Cooler (Tube 59)
      - Sea Plane Hangars by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-F)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, except as noted, 10/27/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 29-1/2x48-1/2 inches
            - Foundation Plan (1), 10/20/1917 (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Floor Plan (2), 10/20/1917 (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Roof Plan (3) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Plan, Elevation and Section of Pylon and Elevation of and Section thro' East and West Walls (5) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Details of Entrance Doorways, Storage Rooms, and Cast Blocks in Brick Pattern Spandrels on all Elevations (6) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Details of Doors and North and South Elevations (7) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Typical Cross-Section and Details of Skylights, Sump, Scuttle and Steel Flagpole (8) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
          - Structural Drawings, except as noted, 10/27/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 29-1/2x48-1/2 inches, except as noted
            - Half-Framing Plan and Roof Framing Plan (1-S) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Truss Schedule (2-S) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Details of Rolling Doors (3-S) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Half-Elevation of East Wall Framing and Details of Trusses and Columns (4-S) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Details of Reinforced Concrete (5-S) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Plan and Section of Crane Platform (6-S), 11/28/1917; 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
          - Mechanical Drawings, 2/7/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 29-1/2x48-1/2 inches
            - Floor Plan (1-M) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
            - Details of Outside Lighting Fixtures, Electric Drive Truck, and Cabinets and Conduit on Columns # 16, 18, & 20 (2-M) (Map-case 26, Folder 12)
      - Technical Stores Building by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-G)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, except as noted, 8/23/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 32x32 inches
            - Floor Plan and Foundation Plan (1), 8/13/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Roof Plan and South and East Elevations (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Section "A-A" and Details of South Elevation and of Cornice and Brick Pattern in Spandrel (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Detail at Entrance Bays (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
          - Structural Drawing, 7/23/1917; ink-on-linen drawing, 31-1/4x31-3/4 inches
            - Roof Framing Plan and Beam and Footing Schedules (1-S), revised 10/31/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
          - Mechanical/Electrical Drawing, 1/14/1918; ink-on-linen drawing, 32x32 inches
            - Plumbing and Heating Plan and Electrical Plan (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
      - Freight and Waiting Room by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 796-I)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, except as noted, 3/8/1918; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 17-1/2x31-1/2 inches
            - Plot Plan and Foundation Plan (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Floor Plan (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Section "B-B" and Roof Plan (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
            - Section on Line "A-A" and Miscellaneous Details (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
          - Mechanical Drawing, 4/12/1918; ink-on-linen drawing, 17-1/2x31-1/2 inches
            - Floor Plan (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 1)
      - Barracks by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 796-K-R)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 4/11/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Plot and Foundation Plans (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Basement and First Floor Plans (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Second Floor Plan and Attic and Roof Plan (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Rear, Front and End Elevations and Section "X-X" (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Miscellaneous Sections (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Interior Details (6) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Exterior Details (7) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Interior and Exterior Details (8) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
          - Structural Drawings, except as noted, 3/25/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Plan of Reinforcing for Basement Floor, Sections and Column Schedule (101-S), 3/27/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - First and Second Floor Framing Plans (102-S) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Half-Plans of Roof and Attic Floor Framing and Details of Trusses and Column Base (103-S) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
          - Mechanical Drawings, 4/2/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Drainage and Basement Plans (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - First and Second Floor Plans (2-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
            - Plot Plan, Heating and Plumbing Riser Diagrams and Detail of Hot Water Heater (3-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 2)
      - Sewage Disposal Building by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 796-L)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 6/13/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 23-1/2x34-1/4 inches
            - Plan and Longitudinal and Cross-Sections (1), revised 7/5/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - Plot Plan, Plan, Roof Framing Plan over Imhoff Tank, Elevations and Sections (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - North, South, West and Door Elevations (3), revised 7/5/1918; 2 drawings (one undated) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
      - Administration Building by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-M)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 11/2/1917; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - First and Second Floor Plans (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - North and South Elevations (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - West Elevation and Sections "A-A" through "D-D" (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - Exterior Details (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
          - Structural Drawings, except as noted, 10/31/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Basement Framing Plan and Column Schedule (1-S), 10/27/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - First Floor Framing Plan and Beam Schedule (2-S) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - Second Floor Framing Plan and Lantern Details (3-S), revised 11/20/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - Roof Framing Plan and Truss Details (4-S) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
          - Mechanical Drawings, 5/21/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 27-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Basement and Attic Plans and Heating and Plumbing Riser Diagrams (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
            - First and Second Floor Plans (2-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 3)
      - Housing Units (Types A, B, C, D, E, I, J, K, L & M) by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-N)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type A and All House Types
          - Architectural Drawings of Housing Unit A, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings,18-1/4x30-3/4 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-A), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - First Floor Plan (2-A), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-A) (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Front Elevation (4-A) (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Rear Elevation (5-A) (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - End Elevation (6-A) (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
          - Architectural Drawings of All House Types, except as noted, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations,18-1/4x30-3/4 inches, except as noted
            - Typical Details for Stairs, Doors, Porches, Walls, and Fireplaces (7-Gen), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Typical Details for Windows, Dormers, Closets and Cupboards (8-Gen) (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Plot Plan (9), revised 7/26/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Plot Plan (10), 3/7/1918; revised 7/26/1918; pencil drawing on paper, 17-1/2x30-1/2 inches (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Plot Plan (11), 3/7/1918; revised 7/26/1918; pencil drawing on paper, 17-1/4x30-1/4 inches (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Plot Plan (12), 2/5/1918; revised 7/26/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Basement Plan for Warm Air Heating for House Types, C, D, J & F (13), 1/7/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Basement Plan for Warm Air Heating for House Types A, B, G, H, K & F (14), 1/7/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - Basement Plan for Warm Air Heating for House Type E (15), 1/7/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types, ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-3/4 inches
            - House Types A, B, G, H, L, & K (1-M), 4/23/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - House Types C, D & J (2-M), 4/24/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - House Type E (3-M), 4/25/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - House Type F (4-M), 4/26/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - House Type I (5-M), 4/26/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
            - House Type M (6-M), 4/27/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 4)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type B
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-B), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - First Floor Plan (2-B), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-B) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Front Elevation (4-B) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Rear Elevation (5-B) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - End Elevation and Sections (6-B) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
              (stored with House Type A)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type C
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-C), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - First Floor Plan (2-C), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-C) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Front Elevation (4-C) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Rear Elevation (5-C) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - End Elevation (6-C) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type D
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-D), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - First Floor Plan (2-D), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-D) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Front Elevation (4-D) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Rear Elevation (5-D) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - End Elevation (6-D) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type E
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/24/1917; electrostatic prints of photostatic prints, 11x17 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-E), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - First Floor Plan (2-E), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-E) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Front Elevation (4-E) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Rear Elevation (5-E) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - End Elevations (6-E) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 5)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type I
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/24/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-I), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - First Floor Plan (2-I), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-I) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Front Elevation (4-I) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Rear Elevation (5-I) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - End Elevation (6-I) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type J
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/29/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-J), undated (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - First Floor Plan (2-J), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type J
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/29/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Second Floor Plan (3-J) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Front Elevation (4-J) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Rear Elevation (5-J) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - End Elevation (6-J) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type K
          - Architectural Drawings, 12/29/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-K), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - First Floor Plan (2-K), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-K) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Front Elevation (4-K), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Rear Elevation (5-K) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - End Elevation (6-K) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 6)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type L
          - Architectural Drawings, 1/11/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-L), revised 1/18/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - First Floor Plan (2-L) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-L) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Front Elevation (4-L) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Rear Elevation (5-L) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - End Elevation (6-L) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
        - Construction Drawings of Housing Unit Type M
          - Architectural Drawings, undated; ink-on-linen drawings, 18-1/4x30-1/2 inches
            - Basement Plan (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - First Floor Plan (2-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Second Floor Plan (3-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Front Elevation (4-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Rear Elevation (5-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - End Elevation (6-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
            - Typical Details, Plot Plans and Mechanical Plans (7-15) (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
          - Mechanical Drawings of Basement Plans for Steam Heating for All House Types (Map-case 27, Folder 7)
      - Commissioned Officers' Quarters by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 796-O)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 4/6/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 24x34-1/2 inches
            - Foundation and Basement Plans (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - First and Second Floor Plans (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - Roof Plan, Section "A-A" and Details of Chimney, Dormers and Interior Trim (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - Window and Other Details (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - Details of Main Entrance and Windows (6) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - Details of Entry and Hall, Dining Room and Kitchen (7) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
          - Structural Drawings, ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 24x34-1/2 inches
            - First and Second Floor Framing Plans (1-S), 3/28/1918; revised 5/26/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - Beam Schedule (2-S), 5/14/1918 (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
          - Mechanical Drawings, 4/10/1918; revised 5/30/1918; ink-on-linen drawings, 24x34-1/4 inches
            - Drainage and Basement Plans (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
            - First and Second Floor Plans (2-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 8)
      - Machine Shop and Engine Storage Building by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-P)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, except as noted, 9/17/1917; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 24x43 inches
            - Foundation Plan (1), 8/13/1917; revised 9/17/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - First Floor Plan (2), revised 11/23/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Roof Plan (3), revised 11/23/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Exterior Elevations and Sections "A-A" and "B-B" (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Plan of Toilet Room and Sections "A-A" through "D-D" (7) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Details of Steel-Sash Doors and Sawtooth Skylight (8) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
          - Structural Drawings, ink-on-linen drawings, 25x43 inches
            - Roof Framing Plan, Sections of Sawtooth Roof and Beam Schedule (1-S), 8/21/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Sections of Sawtooth Roof (2-S), 10/31/1917 (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
          - Mechanical Drawings, undated; ink-on-linen drawings, 24x43 inches
            - First Floor and Fan Room Plans and Details for Heating, Ventilating and Plumbing (1-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - First Floor Electrical Plan (2-M) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
      - Foundry by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ernest Wilby, Associate (Job No. 796-Q)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 11/15/1917; ink-on-linen drawings, 23-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Plot, Foundation, Floor and Roof Plans (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations and Details of Monitor Roof (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Exterior Details (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
            - Longitudinal and Cross-Sections and Miscellaneous Details (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
          - Structural Drawing, 11/15/1917; ink-on-linen drawing with pencil notations, 23-1/2x34-1/2 inches
            - Floor Plan and Details of Trusses (1-S) (Map-case 27, Folder 9)
      - Guard House by Albert Kahn, Architect (Job No. 796-S)
        - Construction Drawings
          - Architectural Drawings, 4/19/1918; ink-on-linen drawings with pencil notations, 18x31-3/4 inches
            - Plot Plan and Foundation Plan (1) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - Floor Plan and Details (2) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - Roof and Roof Framing Plan and Details (3) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - North, South, East and West Elevations (4) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - Details of Colonnade and Column (5) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - Details of Doors, Windows, Walls and Brickwork (6) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)
            - Details of Cells (7) (Map-case 27, Folder 10)